This is Dream Brush.
The system allows me to create a painting by writing Chinese characters with a brush.
I just wrote the character Shan, which means mountain.
[Sound of rock bursting through the ground]
The system generates the painting based on the meaning of the character.
It also generates a sound effect to announce the visual change.
I just wrote Yun, Hai, cloud, and ocean.
[Air whooshing]
The system can automatically separate individual characters from continuous writing.
I just wrote Niao, Ri, bird and the sun.
[Ocean wave crashing and splashing]
The brush allows me to control the size and the location of the generated element using my hand.
[Crane calling]
The output is positioned to match the writing.
I wrote Xue, snow, on top of the existing mountain.
[Rooster crowing]
That's the sound of sunrise.
Metaphorical sounds are generated to depict silent objects.
[Wind howling]
The system understood
I'd like to change the weather for the entire painting.
I just wrote Ye, which means night.
[Cicada chirping]